<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>mysteryfanatist &#8211; NovelFanatist</title>
	<atom:link href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/author/mysteryfanatist/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 08:13:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.com/</generator>
<cloud domain='novelfanatist.wordpress.com' port='80' path='/?rsscloud=notify' registerProcedure='' protocol='http-post' />
<image>
		<url>https://s0.wp.com/i/buttonw-com.png</url>
		<title>mysteryfanatist &#8211; NovelFanatist</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com</link>
	</image>
	<atom:link rel="search" type="application/opensearchdescription+xml" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/osd.xml" title="NovelFanatist" />
	<atom:link rel='hub' href='https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?pushpress=hub'/>
	<item>
		<title>Chapter 1: The beautiful girl at the convenience store.</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-1-the-beautiful-girl-at-the-convenience-store/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-1-the-beautiful-girl-at-the-convenience-store/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[“Didn’t I say I gave you a 10000 yen note!?” At the register of the convenience store, there was a man looking like a blond yankee who was shouting at the top of his voice. It was evening at the convenience store. There were not many customers. A customer who was before me was fighting<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-1-the-beautiful-girl-at-the-convenience-store/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 1: The beautiful girl at the convenience&#160;store."</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>“Didn’t I say I gave you a 10000 yen note!?”</p>



<p>At the register of the convenience store, there was a man looking like a blond yankee who was shouting at the top of his voice.</p>



<p>It was evening at the convenience store.</p>



<p>There were not many customers.</p>



<p>A customer who was before me was fighting at the cash register with a young lady.</p>



<p>“N-no, but I actually only received a 5000 yen bill&#8230;”</p>



<p>“What are you saying!? What I gave you was 1 ten thousand yen bill! It’s not a mistake! Hurry up and give me the remaining 5 thousand!”</p>



<p>“B-but…”</p>



<p>The young lady at the cash register was at a complete loss for what to do.</p>



<p>It’s been an hour since their conversation was moving back and forth.</p>



<p>Really, the talk was really bothersome.</p>



<p>I’m sure that the yankee is making a one sided false accusation.</p>



<p>As I absentmindedly looked at their conversation, I looked at the young lady’s expression.</p>



<p>And I got my heart stolen away.<br /><br />Freely flowing smooth hair.</p>



<p>Black hair that was as beautiful as the hair shown in commercials for shampoo.</p>



<p>Her face was slightly round and she had double edged eyelids.</p>



<p>She has a small nose and slightly thick lips that were shiny pink.</p>



<p>She was a beautiful girl with her parts arranged in a frighteningly neat way.</p>



<p>It feels like she is younger than me?</p>



<p>Is she a high schooler then?</p>



<p>No way she’s the girlfriend of that yankee.</p>



<p>Maybe she is?<br />“I understand. I won’t take money. Instead, Nee-chan, give me your line ID.I’ll forgive you if you do.”</p>



<p>“Eh? Th-that will be a problem…”</p>



<p>She glanced towards the back of the store, towards the break room or the backyard.</p>



<p>Perhaps the manager or a senior staff member was there.</p>



<p>But&#8230; there was no sign of any help coming.</p>



<p>But what did this yankee start saying?</p>



<p>I&#8217;m not sure if he wants money or if he&#8217;s just trying to pick up girls.</p>



<p>I can&#8217;t tolerate either of them.</p>



<p>I had indeed reached the end of my patience.</p>



<p>“Well, brother&#8230; That.”</p>



<p>　I stood next to the Yankee in front of the cash register and pointed to the surveillance camera diagonally above.</p>



<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s a surveillance camera. You can tell at a glance if you&#8217;ve just paid 5,000 yen or 10,000 yen by looking at the recorded video.”</p>



<p>&#8220;What the hell are you doing? Don&#8217;t interfere!”</p>



<p>&#8220;Besides, all the cash registers nowadays are mechanical, so there&#8217;s no way they can mistake whether the money is 5,000 yen or 10,000 yen, right?　If you continue to make things difficult, you&#8217;ll be charged with obstruction of business by force, which is punishable by up to three years in prison or a fine of up to 500,000 yen. If you&#8217;re ready for that, why don&#8217;t you check the surveillance camera footage?&#8221;</p>



<p>Oh, by the way, I&#8217;m a first year law student at university.</p>



<p>The blond Yankee glared at me and then said, &#8220;Damn it! Don’t screw with me!”</p>



<p>&nbsp;The blonde-haired yankee glared at me, then swore, snatched the change off the tray and left.</p>



<p>He swiped the change off the tray and walked out. &#8220;That was… really troublesome, right?&#8221;</p>



<p>I smiled at the beautiful girl at the register.</p>



<p>The girl was staring at me with a blank expression on her face.</p>



<p>Her cheeks were a little pink.</p>



<p>&#8220;Are you okay?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;&#8230;he? Yes, yes! I&#8217;m fwine.”</p>



<p>I put a bottle of water on the register and paid for it with the QR code on my phone.</p>



<p>As I was about to leave, &#8230;&#8230;</p>



<p>&#8220;Um!&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Hmm?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8221; Re-really, thank you so much!&#8221;</p>



<p>　She bowed her head deeply.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s okay. I didn&#8217;t do anything special.&#8221;</p>



<p>　I said, and left the convenience store.</p>



<p>　Wow, it&#8217;s so hot here&#8230;</p>



<p>　In September, Tokyo was still in the throes of midsummer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-1-the-beautiful-girl-at-the-convenience-store/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 15: Caught off guard</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-15-caught-off-guard/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-15-caught-off-guard/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 06:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Konbini JK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=440</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[“W-wait a bit! Why are things suddenly turning out like that?!&#8221; Ayane stood up in front of me and asked out loud. It was lunchtime in the cafeteria of Meisei University. There were many other students around us. Naturally, Ayane was the focus of all their attention. &#8220;C-calm down, Ayane. What&#8217;s the matter? It&#8217;s nothing<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-15-caught-off-guard/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 15: Caught off&#160;guard"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>“W-wait a bit! Why are things suddenly turning out like that?!&#8221; Ayane stood up in front of me and asked out loud.</p>



<p>It was lunchtime in the cafeteria of Meisei University.</p>



<p>There were many other students around us.</p>



<p>Naturally, Ayane was the focus of all their attention.</p>



<p>&#8220;C-calm down, Ayane. What&#8217;s the matter? It&#8217;s nothing to get flustered about, right?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Eh? Ah, yeah. That&#8217;s right&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>Ayane sat there with a slightly gloomy face.</p>



<p>The three of us gathered in the cafeteria for lunch as usual, and I told them the whole story of what happened yesterday.</p>



<p>The moment I finished, Ayane suddenly stood up.</p>



<p>Seiji, who was watching next to her, muttered, &#8220;Now it&#8217;s getting interesting&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Eita, just to confirm&#8230; Was it that beautiful girl, Asuka? And she brought a cake to Eita&#8217;s apartment yesterday?&#8221; Ayane asked me.</p>



<p>&#8220;Ah. Yeah, cheesecake.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t care what it was. It rained so hard that the girl got soaked.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s right.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;So Eita took her into his apartment and made her take a shower.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s right.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Why?!&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Why do you say&#8230;?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Oh, you can&#8217;t let a girl do that, can you? She&#8217;s not even your girlfriend!&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;No, but you know what? If I hadn&#8217;t done that, she would have caught a cold for sure.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yeah, I know, but! Couldn&#8217;t she just give the cake to you and hurry home?&#8221; Ayane said and took a sip of tea from a plastic teacup.&nbsp;</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve got to go to my next class.&#8221;</p>



<p>Ayane then took the tray of lunch she had eaten and quickly left.</p>



<p>It should still be early in the day for her next class&#8230;</p>



<p>&#8220;What&#8217;s really going on? Ayane doesn’t seem like her usual self.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Oh, man, I want to punch this guy.”</p>



<p>&#8220;What?”</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s nothing. Well, good luck!&#8221;</p>



<p>He said, standing up with his tray and tapping me on the shoulder.</p>



<p>====</p>



<p>&#8220;Haaah, I&#8217;ve been caught off guard&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>I arrived early at the large classroom for the next class and sighed loudly.</p>



<p>It even feels a bit like a joke for me.</p>



<p>The moment you fall in love with someone, you can&#8217;t control it.</p>



<p>To be honest, I&#8217;ve been pretty popular since high school.</p>



<p>Not only my looks but also my unnecessarily heavy chest seemed to be attractive to boys.</p>



<p>Even after I entered university, I was still approached by many boys.</p>



<p>On the surface, I&#8217;m friendly with everyone, boys and girls alike.</p>



<p>However&#8230; I sensed a strange ulterior motive from most of the boys.</p>



<p>Trying to get me to drink alcohol when I am underage or lure me out to be alone with me.</p>



<p>I hated it.</p>



<p>If it had been a boy I liked, it might have been another story, but Eita was different.</p>



<p>Now that I remember&#8230; It was just this classroom.</p>



<p>On the surface, I was trying to appear amicable. Yet, in my heart, I had put up a thin barrier between me and others.</p>



<p>Even in this large classroom, I sat alone.</p>



<p>I was listening to the lecture earnestly when I dropped my ballpoint pen trying to get an eraser from my pen case.</p>



<p>The boy next to me, who had taken up one of the seats, picked it up.</p>



<p>ED Note: I feel like this will get interesting.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-15-caught-off-guard/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 14: Hardened Ground after Rainy weather</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-14-hardened-ground-after-rainy-weather/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-14-hardened-ground-after-rainy-weather/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 06:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;I borrowed your hair dryer. My clothes are fine now.&#8221; Asuna-chan smiled. &#8220;But… the blouse is cotton, and it got really wrinkled&#8230; Um, can I just borrow this sweatshirt?&#8221; Asuka-chan held a crumpled white blouse in her hands and asked. &#8220;Give it to me. I&#8217;ll iron it.&#8221; &#8220;What? b-but&#8230;&#8221; &#8220;Don&#8217;t worry. I&#8217;m pretty good at<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-14-hardened-ground-after-rainy-weather/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 14: Hardened Ground after Rainy&#160;weather"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8220;I borrowed your hair dryer. My clothes are fine now.&#8221;</p>



<p>Asuna-chan smiled.</p>



<p>&#8220;But… the blouse is cotton, and it got really wrinkled&#8230; Um, can I just borrow this sweatshirt?&#8221;</p>



<p>Asuka-chan held a crumpled white blouse in her hands and asked.</p>



<p>&#8220;Give it to me. I&#8217;ll iron it.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What? b-but&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Don&#8217;t worry. I&#8217;m pretty good at ironing,&#8221; I said and half-heartedly took the blouse in my hands.</p>



<p>It was a little damp and just right.</p>



<p>I put a cloth over an ironing board and started to iron it with little steam.</p>



<p>&#8220;You&#8217;re good at this. You&#8217;re much better than I am.&#8221;</p>



<p>“Okay, this much is fine. Here. Try it on.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, thank you!&#8221;</p>



<p>Taking her blouse in her hand, Asuka-chan went into the changing room again.</p>



<p>After a while, Asuka-chan came out after she finished changing her clothes.</p>



<p>It was as if a fairy was standing there.</p>



<p>Her beautiful bare legs peeked out from under her mini.</p>



<p>Her blouse was tighter than I expected, with a cute bow around her chest.&nbsp;</p>



<p>I couldn&#8217;t tell when she was wearing a sweatshirt, but the thin waist made her well-shaped breasts stand out.</p>



<p>In addition to that, this well-rounded face&#8230;</p>



<p>&#8220;Do I look weird?&#8221;</p>



<p>She must have felt my gaze on her.</p>



<p>She has her hands clasped behind her back and twists her body slightly as she bends forward.</p>



<p>She was embarrassed, but she kept her knees together and fidgeted.</p>



<p>&#8220;Oh, no, I&#8217;m sorry&#8230; I can&#8217;t see straight&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s a good thing we ate before. If you had been dressed like that, I might not have been able to taste it.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Oh&#8230; Eita-san, that&#8217;s sly&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>Asuka-chan&#8217;s face turned pink again.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s time to go. It&#8217;s dinner time already, and your parents are probably worried about you.&#8221;</p>



<p>I wanted to change the subject for now.</p>



<p>&#8220;Eh? Ah, that&#8217;s true. Then&#8230; I&#8217;ll go back.&#8221;</p>



<p>Asuka-chan&#8217;s expression darkened a little.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s already getting dark outside, so I&#8217;d like to give you a lift if I can.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What? But it&#8217;ll be a bother&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;No, not at all. I&#8217;d be more worried if you had to return alone. I can take you to the nearest convenience store if you want.&#8221;</p>



<p>You might not want people to know where you live.</p>



<p>&#8220;Well&#8230; can I take your word for it?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Okay, let&#8217;s go.</p>



<p>We got ready to go out.</p>



<p>◆◆◆</p>



<p>I&#8217;m glad!</p>



<p>I&#8217;m so happy!</p>



<p>Eita-san&#8230; said he doesn&#8217;t have a girlfriend!</p>



<p>It literally rained, and the ground hardened. [EN: Referring to being nervous, then the situation becomes good.]</p>



<p>He said the cheesecake was delicious.</p>



<p>Eita&#8217;s minestrone was also very tasty.</p>



<p>And&#8230; he said I was cute.</p>



<p>I didn&#8217;t have any makeup on&#8230;</p>



<p>Eita-san may be a natural at it.</p>



<p>Now, Eita-san is taking me home.</p>



<p>I&#8217;m so happy. I almost want to start jumping.</p>



<p>&#8220;Have you already decided on your university program?&#8221; Eita-san asked me as we walked.</p>



<p>&#8220;I haven&#8217;t decided yet, but I&#8217;m thinking about political science and economics.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Oh, that&#8217;s great. You&#8217;re really smart, aren&#8217;t you, Asuka-chan?</p>



<p>By the way, the Faculty of Political Science and Economics is the faculty with the highest variance in value in the humanities at Meisei University.</p>



<p>&#8220;But since Eita-san is a law student, I&#8217;m also interested in law school.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What&#8217;s that? You shouldn&#8217;t do that. You have to decide for yourself.&#8221;</p>



<p>Eita-san laughed and dismissed my true intentions with a simple smile.</p>



<p>“My father runs a trading company, and my mother helps out a little with accounting, so I&#8217;m hoping to do something like that in the future&#8230; In that case, I&#8217;m wondering if it would be better to study economics or commerce.”</p>



<p>&#8220;I see. By the way, do you have siblings?”</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, I have a younger sister. She is in the third year of junior high school, and she also goes to Meisei Junior High School. So next year, she&#8217;ll go through the same escalator as me.”</p>



<p>&#8220;I see, that&#8217;s it.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Actually, both of my parents are Meisei alumni.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Eh? Is that so?”</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes. That&#8217;s why my younger sister and I have both studied at Meisei since junior high school.”</p>



<p>As we walked along, chatting about trivial things, we arrived home in no time.</p>



<p>Checking the time on my phone, I realized that I must have walked for more than 20 minutes.</p>



<p>It usually took me about five minutes to get there.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s a beautiful house.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;The building itself is old, but we renovated the inside. It&#8217;s a three-story building, so it&#8217;s enough for a family of four.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I see. I&#8217;ll see you later.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, I had a good time today. Can I call you again?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, of course.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re going to eat okonomiyaki, right?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What? Oh, yeah, of course.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Have&#8230; you already forgotten?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I remember, I remember. It&#8217;s okay.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Well, excuse me. Thank you for accompanying me.&#8221;</p>



<p>I opened the gate and went inside.</p>



<p>When I closed the door of the house, I gave a small wave to Eita-san.</p>



<p>Eita-san also waved back with that smile.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-14-hardened-ground-after-rainy-weather/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 13: F-First Woman&#8230;</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-13-f-first-woman/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-13-f-first-woman/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Is there anything I can help you with?&#8221; &#8220;I&#8217;m fine. You can sit down.&#8221; We had coffee, tea and two plates of cake. I put them on a large tray and carried them to the table. &#8220;It&#8217;s very well done. Is this cheesecake?&#8221; &#8220;Yes. I hope it&#8217;s to your taste&#8230;&#8221; &#8220;I love cheesecake.&#8221; After we<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-13-f-first-woman/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 13: F-First&#160;Woman&#8230;"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8220;Is there anything I can help you with?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m fine. You can sit down.&#8221;</p>



<p>We had coffee, tea and two plates of cake.</p>



<p>I put them on a large tray and carried them to the table.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s very well done. Is this cheesecake?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes. I hope it&#8217;s to your taste&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I love cheesecake.&#8221;</p>



<p>After we both said, &#8220;thank you for the food&#8221;, I took a bite of the cheesecake.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s delicious!&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Really? I&#8217;m glad&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;It has got just the right amount of sweetness and depth of flavour&#8230; Is it rum?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, it is! How did you know?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yeah. It&#8217;s better than the cheesecake at the restaurant where I work.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s too much of a compliment.&#8221;</p>



<p>We then talked about cakes and cooking.</p>



<p>She likes to make sweets and cook, and I often cook for myself, so we had a lot to talk about in common.</p>



<p>She apologized, &#8220;I&#8217;m kind of sorry about today. I&#8217;m sorry for bothering you&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s fine.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Um&#8230; if you had a girlfriend or something, I thought I&#8217;d apologize.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Haha, I don&#8217;t have a girlfriend.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Is that true?!&#8221;</p>



<p>For some reason, she had the biggest smile of the day.</p>



<p>Nn? Ah. If I had a girlfriend, this situation wouldn&#8217;t be good, right? I think that&#8217;s why she said she didn&#8217;t want to come in.</p>



<p>&#8220;&#8230; Eita-san, I&#8217;m serious.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Isn&#8217;t that normal? Besides&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>I looked upward, searching through my memory.</p>



<p>&#8220;Etto&#8230; You&#8217;re probably the first girl to come into this room. Except for my mother, of course.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What? Are you sure? Yay!&#8221;</p>



<p>She&#8217;s happy to be here.</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve been to Ayane&#8217;s house before, but she’s never been here&#8230; Yeah. You&#8217;re the first woman I had here.&#8221;</p>



<p>“First woman&#8230;&#8221; Asuka blushed.</p>



<p>&#8220;&#8216;No, no, that&#8217;s not what I meant when I said it like that.”</p>



<p>&#8220;He? Y-yes, I&#8217;m sorry&#8230;.&#8221;</p>



<p>She slumped down, with what looked like smoke was coming out of her ears.</p>



<p>&#8220;But&#8230; Ayane-san, is&#8230;. a friend of yours?</p>



<p>&#8220;Eh? Ah, Ayane is a friend of mine from the same department, and the three of us often hang out together with Seiji. She lives in Nakano, and it&#8217;s a good location, so she and Seiji sometimes get together. Ayane&#8217;s apartment is also huge. It&#8217;s about twice the size of this place, I think.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I see.&#8221;</p>



<p>Nakano station is one block away from Shinjuku on the JR Chuo line. It&#8217;s very close to the city center.</p>



<p>Moreover, Ayane&#8217;s apartment is just a two-minute walk from Nakano station.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s such a spacious and well-located condominium. Ayane&#8217;s father actually bought it in cash as an investment when his daughter moved to Tokyo.</p>



<p>In other words, Ayane&#8217;s father is the owner, and the rent and management fees are free.</p>



<p>Incidentally, Ayane&#8217;s father apparently owns nearly ten apartment buildings in the suburbs of Sapporo.</p>



<p>Not ten rooms, but ten buildings.</p>



<p>I guess money is where it&#8217;s at.</p>



<p>In the meantime, I could no longer hear the sound of the futon dryer.</p>



<p>&#8220;Asuka, can you check the clothes for me? If they are half-dry, use the hairdryer.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Oh, sure. If you&#8217;ll excuse me.&#8221;</p>



<p>With that, I walked into the bathroom and closed the door in front of the changing room.</p>



<p>I bring the iron and ironing board from the backroom and get them ready.</p>



<p>I hear the sound of a hairdryer in the changing room.</p>



<p>It must be half-dry, after all, especially if the fabric is thick, like a&#8230; bra.</p>



<p>&#8220;No, no, no.&#8221;</p>



<p>I shake my head and my thoughts.</p>



<p>After a while, Asuka-chan came out of the changing room.</p>



<p>She was wearing a beige-pink miniskirt.</p>



<p>Her thin, fair legs are dazzling.</p>



<p>On top, however, she was still wearing my sweatshirt.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-13-f-first-woman/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 12: P-please don&#8217;t look at me too much&#8230;</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-12-p-please-dont-look-at-me-too-much/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-12-p-please-dont-look-at-me-too-much/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I was in a hurry. I made a soaking wet JK take a shower. One wrong move and it could be a crime&#8230; I can’t think of anything else. Are my t-shirt and sweatshirt&#8230; good enough? Of course, I&#8217;ve already washed them. It&#8217;s just for the time being, so she’ll have to bear with me.<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-12-p-please-dont-look-at-me-too-much/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 12: P-please don&#8217;t look at me too&#160;much&#8230;"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I was in a hurry.</p>



<p>I made a soaking wet JK take a shower.</p>



<p>One wrong move and it could be a crime&#8230;</p>



<p>I can’t think of anything else.</p>



<p>Are my t-shirt and sweatshirt&#8230; good enough?</p>



<p>Of course, I&#8217;ve already washed them.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s just for the time being, so she’ll have to bear with me.</p>



<p>I remembered her body, wet from the rain.</p>



<p>Her slim waist.</p>



<p>Her bare fair legs.</p>



<p>And even the pattern of her&#8230; bra that was showing through.</p>



<p>No!</p>



<p>I shook my head.</p>



<p>Asuka-chan came out of the shower and started the dryer.</p>



<p>I have to dry her clothes in the washing machine first.</p>



<p>From the backroom, I grabbed a drying stand, hangers, and a small white appliance.</p>



<p>&#8220;Can I have a word with you, Asuka?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes!&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;When you&#8217;re done with the dryer, can you hang the laundry here and put it in the bathroom? Then you can set this in the front, okay?&#8221;</p>



<p>I held out the futon dryer.</p>



<p>&#8220;It has a power mode. If you use it, you can get it half-dried in an hour. Then you can use the hairdryer or the iron before you go home.&#8221;</p>



<p>I sometimes use this futon dryer to dry my laundry. Although, it consumes a lot of electricity, so it does cost me a lot.</p>



<p>I can&#8217;t say that now, because it&#8217;s an emergency situation.</p>



<p>&#8220;I could do it myself, but&#8230; you have&#8230; underwear to dry too, right?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Eh? Ah, yes&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;So, I&#8217;ll show you how to use it, and you can do what you can, okay?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes! Thank you very much.&#8221;</p>



<p>I said that and explained to her how to use the futon dryer.</p>



<p>I turned on the ventilation fan in the bathroom.</p>



<p>&#8220;Do you like vegetable soup, Asuka-chan?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I made minestrone yesterday, and I have some leftovers. I&#8217;ll warm some of it up.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I see. I&#8217;d love to have some.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Okay. Okay. I&#8217;ll heat it up,&#8221; I said and went back to the kitchen.</p>



<p>I prepared two mugs of minestrone and put them in the microwave.</p>



<p>Just as I heard the microwave&#8217;s tone, Asuka-chan came back.</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m sorry about everything that happened today.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Is your body okay?”</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, I warmed up a lot in the shower.&#8221;</p>



<p>There was a small table and two chairs in front of the kitchen.</p>



<p>I asked Asuka-chan to sit there.</p>



<p>I took out two bowls of minestrone from the microwave and put them on the table together with spoons.</p>



<p>I sat across from her.</p>



<p>&#8220;It might be hot, so be careful.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Thank you very much, and thank you for the food.&#8221;</p>



<p>We both drink the minestrone.</p>



<p>&#8220;Delicious&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m glad. My parents send me vegetables and rice on a regular basis. So before the vegetables get bad, I often make soup like this. I also make okonomiyaki.&#8221; [EN: It&#8217;s like a pancake dish with toppings such as meat and some vegetables.]</p>



<p>&#8220;Ah, okonomiyaki, that sounds delicious!&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Do you want to have it sometime later?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;What? Is that okay?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Of course. I&#8217;ll call you when I make it.&#8221;</p>



<p>I look at Asuka-chan again.</p>



<p>She had just finished showering and had no makeup on.</p>



<p>Yet, her fair skin is beautiful, and her double eyelids are lovely.</p>



<p>The parts of her body are well proportioned, making her as beautiful as a celebrity.</p>



<p>I wondered if she felt my gaze on her.</p>



<p>Her cheeks flushed a little, and she turned her head away.</p>



<p>Asuka-chan hid her face with her hands.</p>



<p>She was red up to the tips of her ears.</p>



<p>&#8220;What you brought for me was a cake, right? I put it in the fridge.&#8221;</p>



<p>I have to change the subject.</p>



<p>&#8220;What? Ah, yes.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Shall we have it after the soup?”</p>



<p>&#8220;Is it okay If I join?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Sure, I&#8217;ll eat with you. Would you like a cup of tea or coffee? I have apple juice too.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Can I have some tea, please?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Understood.&#8221;</p>



<p>After finishing the soup, I went to the kitchen and turned on the kettle.</p>



<p>I prepared tea and coffee.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-12-p-please-dont-look-at-me-too-much/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 11: It was a huge failure&#8230;</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-11-it-was-a-huge-failure/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-11-it-was-a-huge-failure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s unexpected&#8230; A huge failure&#8230; It&#8217;s a minus 10,000 out of 100 points&#8230; I&#8217;m currently taking a shower in Eita-san&#8217;s apartment. I don&#8217;t know how this happened. I finished school and rushed home. I wore a flared mini skirt and a white blouse, as well as some light makeup. I had to show off my<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-11-it-was-a-huge-failure/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 11: It was a huge&#160;failure&#8230;"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It&#8217;s unexpected&#8230;</p>



<p>A huge failure&#8230;</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a minus 10,000 out of 100 points&#8230;</p>



<p>I&#8217;m currently taking a shower in Eita-san&#8217;s apartment.</p>



<p>I don&#8217;t know how this happened.</p>



<p>I finished school and rushed home.</p>



<p>I wore a flared mini skirt and a white blouse, as well as some light makeup.</p>



<p>I had to show off my neatness.</p>



<p>I checked my whole body in the mirror.</p>



<p>I thought I looked good.</p>



<p>I wondered if he would think my legs were beautiful.</p>



<p>Holding the cake in my hand, I left the house a little nervous, so I didn&#8217;t have time to look at the weather forecast at all.</p>



<p>After about five minutes of walking, dark clouds quickly gathered.</p>



<p>I quickened my pace.</p>



<p>But after another five minutes of walking, I saw&#8230;</p>



<p>DOGOON!</p>



<p>&#8220;Kyaaaah!&#8221;</p>



<p>It started to rain like a waterfall.</p>



<p>I looked for a place where I could take shelter from the rain, but this was a residential area, and I couldn&#8217;t find such a place.</p>



<p>Should I go back home?</p>



<p>But this is right in the middle of nowhere.</p>



<p>Hopefully, it&#8217;s just a passing shower, and it stops soon.</p>



<p>Besides, Eita-san is waiting for me.</p>



<p>I ran faster and faster, looking for a place to take shelter from the rain.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, the rain was getting heavier and heavier.</p>



<p>In the end, I couldn&#8217;t take shelter from the rain even once and ended up at Eita-san&#8217;s apartment.</p>



<p>Eita-san was waiting for me outside.</p>



<p>The rain had robbed me of my body heat, and I was cold and shivering a little.</p>



<p>Worried about me, Eita-san took me into his room.&nbsp;</p>



<p>He said, &#8220;You&#8217;d better take a shower, Asuka. Let&#8217;s put all your clothes in the washing machine and let them dry for now.&#8221;</p>



<p>Then, he pushed the button on the washing machine next to the bathroom and set it to drying mode.</p>



<p>&#8220;Since it&#8217;s an&#8230; emergency, are you okay with wearing my t-shirt and sweatshirt?&#8221;</p>



<p>Eita-san pulled out a slightly thicker sweatshirt, a t-shirt and a bath towel from the closet at the back of the room and handed them to me.</p>



<p>&#8220;Put the clothes in the washing machine and press this button. Then you can take a shower and warm up.&#8221;</p>



<p>Eita-san said, his face crumpling up in a small smile.</p>



<p>Oh, he&#8217;s still so kind&#8230;</p>



<p>That smile alone warmed my heart a little.</p>



<p>But my body was still cold.</p>



<p>In the end, I took everything that was wearing off, put it in the washing machine, and decided to use the shower without hesitation.</p>



<p>Suddenly, I was in a man&#8217;s house, and he was letting me use his shower.</p>



<p>It happened too fast.</p>



<p>No, that&#8217;s not how it happened.</p>



<p>But what should I do after showering?</p>



<p>There are so many things I was thinking about, and my mind is in a panic.</p>



<p>I wonder how long I had been in the shower.</p>



<p>I stopped showering when my body had warmed up considerably, and I took the t-shirt and sweatshirt.</p>



<p>These are Eita-san&#8217;s clothes.</p>



<p>I would have preferred his shirt anyway&#8230;</p>



<p>But wait, I&#8217;m not going to wear a bra or panties, aren&#8217;t I?</p>



<p>&#8230; I&#8217;m glad it was a sweatshirt.</p>



<p>The fabric is a thick one, so I don&#8217;t think it will show any fine lines.</p>



<p>I wore the t-shirt and then a sweatshirt over it.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s too big.</p>



<p>I can&#8217;t get my hands out of my sleeves.</p>



<p>I had no choice but to bend the pant hems and sleeves twice.</p>



<p>There was a hairdryer near the sink.</p>



<p>I asked, &#8220;Um&#8230; May I borrow the hairdryer?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, of course.&#8221;</p>



<p>I went to the mirror and borrowed the hairdryer.</p>



<p>I could see myself a little gloomy in the mirror, with no makeup on my face.</p>



<p>I wondered where my merriness from before I left the house had gone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-11-it-was-a-huge-failure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 10: You&#8217;re lying, right?</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/youre-lying-right/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/youre-lying-right/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I was very excited. After class, I walked quickly to the station and boarded the Chuo Line. As it would seem, she would arrive at my apartment around 4:30. I have plenty of time to get ready. Even though it was the beginning of October, it was still hot. Today&#8217;s temperature was 32 Celsius. [EN:<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/youre-lying-right/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 10: You&#8217;re lying,&#160;right?"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I was very excited.</p>



<p>After class, I walked quickly to the station and boarded the Chuo Line.</p>



<p>As it would seem, she would arrive at my apartment around 4:30. I have plenty of time to get ready.</p>



<p>Even though it was the beginning of October, it was still hot. Today&#8217;s temperature was 32 Celsius. [EN: 90°F]</p>



<p>The ground felt like it was boiling.</p>



<p>When I left the campus, the weather was clear and sunny, but when I arrived at Nishiogikubo, the clouds looked a little suspicious.</p>



<p>&#8220;I hope it doesn&#8217;t rain.&#8221;</p>



<p>I hurried home, wishing that it wouldn&#8217;t rain.</p>



<p>Thinking that maybe Asuka-chan will come up to my room, I wanted to keep the place as clean as possible.</p>



<p>I arrived at my apartment at half-past four.</p>



<p>Thank God it was not a mess.</p>



<p>I should prepare something to drink. There&#8217;s only apple juice in the fridge.</p>



<p>Would a warm drink be better?</p>



<p>While thinking, I looked out the window.</p>



<p>What? It&#8217;s cloudy.</p>



<p>It was so sunny a while ago&#8230;</p>



<p>The moment I thought that,</p>



<p>BOOOM!</p>



<p>The moment the lightning struck down, I heard the tremendous rumble of thunder and then it started to rain.</p>



<p>It was raining unbelievably hard.</p>



<p>Thirty seconds later, the rain was like a bucket that was flipped upside down.</p>



<p>It was a guerrilla downpour. [EN: The kind that would be taken advantage of in guerrilla tactics.]</p>



<p>I couldn&#8217;t see past 50 meters from the window because of the rain.</p>



<p>I hurriedly grabbed my phone.</p>



<p>Eita: It&#8217;s raining like hell. It’s fine if you don’t come.</p>



<p>I sent a message, but it wasn&#8217;t read.</p>



<p>Wait a minute.</p>



<p>She said she was going to walk over, right?</p>



<p>Is there a good chance that she has already left the house?</p>



<p>I got impatient.</p>



<p>Even if I had an umbrella, I&#8217;d probably still get pretty wet.</p>



<p>There was also a strong crosswind, and I was also worried about lightning.</p>



<p>I grabbed two umbrellas and opened the door.</p>



<p>It was raining so hard that I couldn&#8217;t hear anything around me.</p>



<p>If I could, I would have picked her up.</p>



<p>But then I realized something.</p>



<p>Where is Asuka-chan’s house?</p>



<p>I don&#8217;t know where she&#8217;s coming from or what route she&#8217;s taking.</p>



<p>If I go looking for her, there&#8217;s a chance we&#8217;ll end up passing by each other.</p>



<p>&#8220;I guess I&#8217;ll have to wait after all&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>I stood outside the door with my umbrella in my hand.</p>



<p>◆◆◆</p>



<p>I continued to wait outside the door, phone in hand.</p>



<p>The rain was getting heavier.</p>



<p>The sound of the rain was so loud that I could hardly hear what was going on around me.</p>



<p>It was a guerrilla downpour like I&#8217;ve never experienced before.</p>



<p>The LINE message was still unread.</p>



<p>It had been about ten minutes.</p>



<p>In the pouring rain, a girl with black hair arrived running from the left road in front of my apartment.</p>



<p>She was carrying something in her arms… and was without an umbrella.</p>



<p>&#8220;You&#8217;re kidding, right?&#8221;</p>



<p>I dash down the stairs of my apartment with my umbrella in my hand.</p>



<p>It might not be Asuka-chan, but it didn&#8217;t matter.</p>



<p>She looked up at me as I came down the stairs.</p>



<p>It was a soaking wet Asuka-chan.</p>



<p>Did you come without an umbrella in this rain?</p>



<p>It feels almost suicidal.</p>



<p>She was wet to an impressive extent. It was as if you were thrown into a pool as punishment.</p>



<p>The white blouse stuck to her body, basically transparent enough to see her cami and bra.</p>



<p>&#8220;Asuka-chan!&#8221;</p>



<p>I tilted the umbrella I was holding towards her.</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m sorry! I didn&#8217;t see the weather forecast&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>She was already half-crying.</p>



<p>&#8220;I-if you&#8217;re okay, please eat this later. Okay then!&#8221;</p>



<p>She pushed the bag she was holding so carefully to me and tried to leave.</p>



<p>&#8220;Wait a minute! You&#8217;ll catch a cold if you go home like this. Even lightning is dangerous. Just come up.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;But, aren&#8217;t I bothering you&#8230;?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;You&#8217;re not bothering me. Anyway, hurry up.&#8221;</p>



<p>I half-heartedly pulled the hesitant Asuka-chan into the room.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/youre-lying-right/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 9: Good Job, me!</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-9-good-job-me/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-9-good-job-me/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=423</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;What kind of message should I send&#8230;?&#8221; It has been a few days since I&#8217;ve talked to Seiji about the situation. I hadn&#8217;t been able to get in touch with Asuka. She was a schoolgirl. An exceptional beauty at that. If I were to send her a strange message, she might laugh at me, although<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-9-good-job-me/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 9: Good Job,&#160;me!"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8220;What kind of message should I send&#8230;?&#8221;</p>



<p>It has been a few days since I&#8217;ve talked to Seiji about the situation.</p>



<p>I hadn&#8217;t been able to get in touch with Asuka.</p>



<p>She was a schoolgirl.</p>



<p>An exceptional beauty at that.</p>



<p>If I were to send her a strange message, she might laugh at me, although I don&#8217;t think she&#8217;s that kind of girl.</p>



<p>It was afternoon break time at the university campus.</p>



<p>I was absentmindedly thinking about it as I looked at Asuka&#8217;s contact on LINE.</p>



<p>That&#8217;s when I heard a &#8216;Zupon!&#8217; from my phone.</p>



<p>“Nn?”</p>



<p>Asuna: &#8216;Hello. I baked a cake yesterday, but it&#8217;s too much for just me. Could you please take half of it? I&#8217;ll bring it to you this evening!&#8217;</p>



<p>“Uwah…”</p>



<p>She contacted me.</p>



<p>But&#8230; I honestly appreciate it.</p>



<p>Asuka-chan also has class today, right?</p>



<p>She&#8217;s bringing it to me after school.</p>



<p>I don&#8217;t have a part-time job today.</p>



<p>If I go home right after class, I&#8217;ll be at my apartment by five.</p>



<p>I hastily typed a reply.</p>



<p>Eita: &#8216;Thank you. But is it really okay? I&#8217;d really like to eat it. Do you want me to meet you somewhere in the evening?&#8217;</p>



<p>Asuka: &#8216;If it&#8217;s not too much trouble, I&#8217;ll bring it to Eita-san&#8217;s apartment. It&#8217;s close, and I can walk there.&#8217;</p>



<p>&#8220;Eh? Is that okay&#8230;?&#8221;</p>



<p>She knows where my apartment is, so it&#8217;s no problem for her to come.</p>



<p>It’s just&#8230;</p>



<p>I don&#8217;t think it&#8217;s the right choice to pick it up at the door and say, &#8220;Yes, goodbye.&#8221;</p>



<p>The development of her coming into my room and saying, “Shall we eat this cake together?” might happen…</p>



<p>I remembered the state of my room.</p>



<p>The room shouldn&#8217;t be too messy.</p>



<p>My bed is on top of the loft, so it shouldn&#8217;t be a problem.</p>



<p>The laundry is hanging outside.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s&#8230; probably fine..&#8221;</p>



<p>Of course, if she said she was leaving, that would be fine.</p>



<p>I hasten my reply.</p>



<p>Eita: &#8216;Thanks. Is it really okay? Then, I&#8217;ll take your word for it and wait for you at the apartment, say around five?&#8217;</p>



<p>When I typed that, a stamp of a bear bowing down came back saying, &#8220;Thank you very much.”</p>



<p>&nbsp;◆◆◆</p>



<p>Yes! I did it! Good job, me!</p>



<p>After much thought, I sent the simplest message possible.</p>



<p>I felt like an idiot for thinking about it so much.</p>



<p>And it&#8217;s for&#8230; this evening!</p>



<p>Now, to choose what to wear.</p>



<p>I want him to see me looking as cute as possible.</p>



<p>Should I choose neat and clean? Does Eita-san like people who dress more like adults?</p>



<p>For now, since it&#8217;s the first private outing, neat and clean is the safest choice.</p>



<p>And the skirt should be a mini.</p>



<p>Mini is the only choice.</p>



<p>There was a beige-pink flared mini skirt.</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s go with that.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ll go for it with my bare legs! [TL Note: Meaning that she’s going to not wear anything like stockings or socks.]</p>



<p>For the top&#8230; I’ll choose a white blouse with a cute bow on the chest.</p>



<p>I was in class but couldn’t hear what the teacher said.</p>



<p>That&#8217;s how happy I was.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-9-good-job-me/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 8:Contact her immediately!</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-8contact-her-immediately/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-8contact-her-immediately/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=421</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It was a little after 9:30 at night. After punching in my time card, Seiji and I went out the back door. The night breeze felt good on my tired and burning cheeks. &#8220;By the way, Eita, have you been in touch with that beautiful girl?” &#8220;No… We haven&#8217;t contacted each other lately.” “You! Why<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-8contact-her-immediately/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 8:Contact her&#160;immediately!"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It was a little after 9:30 at night.</p>



<p>After punching in my time card, Seiji and I went out the back door.</p>



<p>The night breeze felt good on my tired and burning cheeks.</p>



<p>&#8220;By the way, Eita, have you been in touch with that beautiful girl?”</p>



<p>&#8220;No… We haven&#8217;t contacted each other lately.”</p>



<p>“You! Why is that?”</p>



<p>No, I don&#8217;t want to be told that with such vigour.</p>



<p>That night, I received a message that said, &#8220;Thank you so much for today!&#8221; so I gave her a random reply and never saw her again.</p>



<p>&#8220;Eita, you don&#8217;t have a girlfriend right now, do you? It&#8217;s not every day you find a beautiful girl like her.”</p>



<p>&#8220;No, well, that may be true. What about Seiji? Are you in touch with that girl, Eri-chan?”</p>



<p>I avert the subject.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s obvious, right? I can&#8217;t leave a cute little girl like that alone. The only thing is that Eri is pretty tough. I&#8217;m not sure what to do. Maybe she&#8217;s more used to men than we think.”</p>



<p>You&#8217;re playing like this, Seiji? Amazing.</p>



<p>Eri-chan, you are to be feared.</p>



<p>&#8220;Don&#8217;t worry about me. Eita, are you going to leave this chance to pass by?&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;No, but is there a chance? Besides, I don&#8217;t know what she thinks of me either&#8230; I was just helping out.”</p>



<p>&#8220;This is why Eita is so&#8230;.&#8221;</p>



<p>Seiji&#8217;s pose, along the &#8216;Yare yare,&#8217; makes me feel endlessly depressed.</p>



<p>&#8220;Did you see the look on her face? That&#8217;s the expression of a woman in love and not only that&#8230; Ah, screw it! It&#8217;s a sin not to contact her anyway! Get in touch with her immediately!&#8221;</p>



<p>I don&#8217;t know what it was, but Seiji was screaming at me.</p>



<p>I was too busy replying with a &#8220;&#8230; I&#8217;ll do my best.”</p>



<p>◆◆◆</p>



<p>After eating lunch during lunch break, I worked hard on a text with my phone in hand.</p>



<p>&#8220;You haven&#8217;t sent it yet?&#8221;</p>



<p>I heard Eri&#8217;s exasperated voice next to me.</p>



<p>She&#8217;s in my class, and we always eat lunch together.</p>



<p>“Saying something like that….”</p>



<p>“If it were that easy, I wouldn’t have any trouble sending it.”</p>



<p>“What if you send a, &#8216;I love you&#8230; chuu~♡&#8217;?”</p>



<p>“O-of course I can’t do that!”</p>



<p>Sometimes Eri is so mean.</p>



<p>“But I was really surprised. At that time, I didn&#8217;t know that Asuka would ask for his LINE like that. You&#8217;ve never done that before.”</p>



<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s true, but&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve never tried asking for a guy&#8217;s contact information before, as Eri said.</p>



<p>But at that time, I thought, &#8216;Never being able to see him again&#8230; I don’t want that!&#8217; and decided to ask him.</p>



<p>Even though we had exchanged LINE&#8230;</p>



<p>After I sent him a thank you message that day, I still hadn&#8217;t been able to get in touch with Eita.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve been writing and deleting LINE messages repeatedly.</p>



<p>I didn&#8217;t know that it was so difficult to send a message to a guy without any particular reason.</p>



<p>I knew I needed an excuse.</p>



<p>So I baked a cheesecake yesterday. It turned out very well.</p>



<p>I want to deliver it as soon as possible since it is a perishable product.</p>



<p>All I have to do is contact them via LINE and deliver it to him&#8230;</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve been thinking about my message since yesterday, but I&#8217;m still not sure how to write it.</p>



<p>&#8220;By the way, Eri, are you in contact with this Seiji-san?”</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes. He sent me a message as soon as he could. I&#8217;ve been replying to his messages at random. He&#8217;s a playful guy, so it&#8217;s like we&#8217;ve been keeping in touch. But I heard that he sometimes drives his car home. It might come in handy in case of an emergency.”</p>



<p>That&#8217;s right, Eri was this kind of girl.</p>



<p>She’s not a bad girl. But how do I explain it…. She doesn’t have an interest in a boyfriend, it seems.</p>



<p>I was going to stare at the phone for a little while longer.</p>



<p>If I don’t send a message fast&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-8contact-her-immediately/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 7: There is a chance, right?</title>
		<link>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-7-there-is-a-chance-right/</link>
					<comments>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-7-there-is-a-chance-right/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mysteryfanatist]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/?p=419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chapter 7: There is a chance, right? Eita-san and I walked back together. We were able to talk a lot. He casually walked on the side of the road and seemed to be&#8230; protecting me, which made my heart skip a beat. I think I might be a little simple-minded, but I even found out<a class="more-link" href="https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-7-there-is-a-chance-right/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">"Chapter 7: There is a chance,&#160;right?"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Chapter 7: There is a chance, right?</p>



<p>Eita-san and I walked back together.</p>



<p>We were able to talk a lot.</p>



<p>He casually walked on the side of the road and seemed to be&#8230; protecting me, which made my heart skip a beat.</p>



<p>I think I might be a little simple-minded, but I even found out what apartment he lives in!</p>



<p>And&#8230; saw that his underwear was boxer shorts&#8230;</p>



<p>Eita-san is from Nagano and is a simple, nice person.</p>



<p>He told me that he works part-time at a restaurant in Kichijoji.</p>



<p>I would like to visit that restaurant next time.</p>



<p>I wonder how he&#8217;d look in a garçon apron or the outwear?</p>



<p>H-He&#8217;ll definitely look cool! I feel like I&#8217;ll take a lot of pictures.&nbsp;</p>



<p>I heard from him that he cooks his own food, seems to be an independent adult and that he also likes sweets.</p>



<p>But I couldn&#8217;t ask him about the important things.</p>



<p>Like&#8230; whether&#8230; he has something like a girlfriend.</p>



<p>Since he’s such a wonderful person, it wouldn’t be surprising if he has one.</p>



<p>However, I&#8217;m confident that if he did… I&#8217;d be sulking in bed for days.</p>



<p>Should I just casually ask him on LINE?</p>



<p>I myself have never been with a boy before.</p>



<p>I go to a co-ed school, and I&#8217;ve had boys confess their feelings for me, but I&#8217;ve turned them all down. The boys in my grade&#8230; stand out as either childish and naive or as flashy and daring.</p>



<p>I don&#8217;t feel like I can talk to them openly at all.</p>



<p>But&#8230; Eita-san is an adult!&nbsp;</p>



<p>I can&#8217;t believe he&#8217;s only one year older than me.</p>



<p>Just by being with him, I felt a sense of ease and security enveloping me&#8230;</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve never felt like this before.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve just found the apartment where he lives. It&#8217;s only a 20-minute walk from my house.</p>



<p>Isn&#8217;t this a good chance?</p>



<p>If I make him something sweet and bring it to him, will he eat it?</p>



<p>◆◆◆</p>



<p>&#8220;Order up! Number three, one codfish with cream, one grilled squid, one Caesar, and one Margherita pizza!&#8221;</p>



<p>I shouted to the kitchen, passing the order.</p>



<p>Trattoria Vicino.</p>



<p>Trattoria Vicino is a hidden Italian restaurant in Kichijoji.</p>



<p>Seiji and I currently work on the floor there.</p>



<p>Even though it was a weekday, the place was pretty crowded around seven o&#8217;clock.</p>



<p>The restaurant has pasta and pizza and is reasonably priced.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a perfect place to eat in this area with many students.</p>



<p>I just listen to orders, pass them through to the kitchen, serve them, and take them away when done.</p>



<p>When the time is right, I go to the kitchen to fill up on cold drinks, checking the bill as I pass by.</p>



<p>It is a repetitive process.</p>



<p>After 8:30, the number of customers coming in finally slowed down.</p>



<p>Hiding in the shadows of the kitchen, Seiji and I rehydrated ourselves.</p>



<p>&#8220;Well, it&#8217;s been another busy day, hasn&#8217;t it?</p>



<p>The person who came to talk to us with a smile was Shiori Date-san, a fourth-year student at another university and our manager.</p>



<p>She has been working here for a long time.</p>



<p>&#8220;Yes, and there were two groups.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;Yeah, I had to go back and get the order several times, too. I wish they would just order all at once&#8230;&#8221;</p>



<p>Both Seiji and I complained, partly because we were tired.</p>



<p>&#8220;Haha, don&#8217;t say that. You&#8217;re contributing to the sales.”</p>



<p>Shiori-san, who is smiling, is not that much taller than me. Probably around 170 centimetres or more.</p>



<p>She ties her long black hair in a ponytail while working, her face is sculpted, and she is more handsome than beautiful.</p>



<p>Even if she stood on Takarazuka Revue, she wouldn&#8217;t look out of place at all. [EN: Takarazuka Revue is an all-female musical theatre, even for male characters.]</p>



<p>Shiori-san, a fourth-year student, was offered a job at a major trading company.</p>



<p>Both Seiji and I have been indebted to Shiori-san since we started working here.</p>



<p>It makes me sad to think that we will only be working together for another six months.</p>



<p>&#8220;Now then, why don&#8217;t you two get to work on the cleanup? I&#8217;ll take your orders.</p>



<p>&#8220;I understand.&#8221;&nbsp;</p>



<p>&#8220;Understood.&#8221;</p>



<p>We both regained our enthusiasm.</p>



<p>ED Note: The restaurant actually exists, lol.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://novelfanatist.wordpress.com/2021/09/03/chapter-7-there-is-a-chance-right/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		
		<media:content url="https://1.gravatar.com/avatar/7ef3ad7362c3b45510bae4c609d7dec3?s=96&#38;d=identicon&#38;r=G" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mysteryfanatist</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
